all right thank you and uh I hope
everyone had a good
lunch good food interesting
conversations luckily not interesting
food okay um yeah so uh welcome back to
our sessions uh our first speaker is
palavi parel uh she's with yel
uh works on the as a tech lead on the
search quality team and uh I really find
interesting what you wrote in your short
bio uh so uh she builds backend
solutions that powers youx features uh
on search result page that sounds super
interesting so please welcome um
palavi so yeah I've been in this space
for over 5 years now at galp where I've
primarily worked on user facing
Solutions in the relevant space and I'm
actually going to be talking about one
of those uh problem areas today
specifically relevance proof in Yelp
search with a focus on LM powerered
annotations so this is kind of the
agenda that you'll see throughout uh the
rest of the talk in a minute I'll get
started by setting some context on Yelp
search and what annotations even are and
then we'll spend most of the talk
talking about um llm expansions and how
we've leveraged them for a couple of
annotations and then finally towards the
end I'll talk about the future of
annotations a little bit and also a
little bit about how we've leveraged The
annotation system for rag so to get
things started what is the
Yelp uh this is a screenshot of one of
yelp's pages on web so kind of in one
sentence Yelp connects people with great
local businesses uh so businesses can
jump on to Yelp and have their own pages
on Yelp where they provide information
about themselves so what what's on their
menu what services do they offer what
are their open RS what kinds of payments
do they accept and then users when they
either visit these businesses or use
their services can write reviews for the
business and
so what Yelp search does is connects
users of Yelp with those businesses that
they're looking for so we want to find
whatever businesses satisfy your search
query which is what you're going to type
in when you jump onto Yelp and sort of
open this search view up you might be
looking for a new restaurant if you want
to try some new food in which case your
search results might look something like
this page in the middle over here or
maybe you're having some plumbing issue
at home know and you need a plumber so
you come on to search type plumbers and
you see something that looks slightly
different more specific to your
intent so just to uh set some quick
context I'm sure most of you know this
term already but I'm going to be saying
the word Ser a lot so Ser stands for
search engine results page so when you
run a search businesses are retrieved
and ranked based on the query that
you've run and then they're displayed to
you on the surp right so let's say you
ran a search like Korean corn dogs in
the image over here you might see some
results that look like this for the sake
of this example I've hidden some
information so just imagine if you had
run the search and all you saw on the
page were these results with none no
other information right so it looks like
these businesses are kind of relevant to
what you've searched for from like the
images and the categories but it's not
sort of like 100% confirmed from just
the information that you can
see so that's actually where annotations
come in handy and we're going to talk
about that
next so annotations provide some um
additional information about a search
result these annotations could be of
various types as you can see in the
screenshots over here there's like quite
a few in sort of the highlighted boxes
and these might provide relevance proof
that the business is relevant to the
user query they might provide some
unique information about the businesses
or they might have some personal appeal
like the one you can see for happy hour
which might be shown to you because we
know you as a Yelp user like
AP and then one specific type of
annotation that I want to talk more
about is called review highlights so
these are spans or sentences of text
pulled from business reviews and these
are then shown on search results to
provide extra context about those search
results and often times you'll see that
these review highlights have a bolded
word or phrase in this case Pizza which
proves that the search result is
relevant to the search
query so now that we've seen a bit of
what annotations are and seen a couple
of
examples what makes a good annotation so
Yelp has two responsibilities here we
have a responsibility towards the
business we want to portray them
accurately right but we also have a
responsibility to the user we want to
provide them with the right information
so that they can make their decision and
like have a successful session on yel so
with that in mind we have a PRI rough
prioritization in our mind for the types
of annotations that we would like to
show so first and foremost we would like
to show an annotation that confirms that
the business is relevant to the search
query that the user has run secondly our
other priority would be to show
something interesting or unique about
the business so what sets the business
apart from the other businesses on the
page and then finally we might also show
supplementary information about the
business this might not be something
super interesting or unique about the
business but just something that we feel
is necessary for this type of query
maybe so these product principles that I
just spoke about they're baked into a
service that we have called the
annotator service and given a business
that is going to be shown on the Ser the
annotator service is responsible for
pulling in a bunch of information about
that business and then building an
exhaustive list of annotations that it
could show for that business and then it
uses those three priorities or
principles that I mentioned to choose
choose the the few essential annotations
that it ends up showing on the Sur for
that
result so given all of uh this context
on the product principles and how the
annotator service works we can then
revisit the Korean cond dogs example
that we saw before and now I've removed
those like Dark boxes that were hiding
things and you can see that both of the
businesses that we've shown actually
have these annotations on them that
satisfy those product principles that we
spoke about so on each of the results
you can see that the first annotation
that we've shown does indeed provide
that relevance proof it's showing that
both of these businesses do serve Korean
corn
dogs so many years ago when we uh kind
of started thinking about annotation
we as we were sort of building out our
road map the first step was starting
with very fix or structured annotations
just built on the data that all of the
businesses had and those looked
something like this first box over here
so we still have these types of
annotations you've seen them in some of
the screenshots that I've already shown
but for the last couple of years we've
been more focused on on uh building more
intelligence into our annotations so one
thing that that uh sort of involves is
leveraging more Community content and
then another aspect of it is also being
more aware of the user intent or like
the query context and that's going to be
the focus for most of the rest of the
presentation and then finally in our
road map we of course have a vision for
the future in which we are always
talking about continuously iterating so
uh I'll talk a bit more about that
future towards the end of the
presentation cool so before we can
really dive into talking about llm
powered annotations I just want to give
a brief overview of query understanding
and how we use that to build llm query
expansions so um like we discussed
before there are certain priorities by
which we decide which annotations are
relevant right but in order to even know
if an annotation is relevant or not we
really need to understand what users are
looking for on Yelp in the first place
so when users land on Yelp search they
could have a variety of intents so this
is just like a quick snapshot of some of
them but you know users might be
searching for a specific category of
businesses like dentists or a particular
dish like mango sticky rice a service
like custom landscaping or you know they
might have like
more uh sort of multi-word queries where
either they're searching for like a
broad uh type of business like things to
do as a tourist in London or they're
going very specific right like a
restaurant for a wedding reception and
so we really need to think about each of
these cases and understand uh deeply
what the user is looking
for so what exactly are query highlight
expansions so given a user intent or a
user search query we want to come up
with a set of phrases such that a
suggested phrase can be highlighted on
the search result in order to prove its
relevance to the user's search query so
what might this intuition look like so
for something like Starbucks for example
pretty simple query um users might be
interested in seeing the word Starbucks
itself highlighted but also they might
be interested in seeing the categories
of the business like cafes and breakfast
or offerings from the business like
coffee tea and muffins these words might
also be important to highlight right so
that was a pretty easy example but what
about something a little more
complicated like affordable hair salons
so extrapolating from what we spoke
about for Starbucks already obviously
hair salon hair cut blowout and so on is
important to highlight but most
importantly the word affordable is key
here right so when you look at the
results for affordable hair salons
you're obviously going to see a bunch of
hair salons and it's going to be pretty
clear that these are hair salons but the
user is looking for affordable hair
salons and so the key word that we
really care about highlighting here is
Affordable and so the most important
thing would be affordable cheap value
for money or other synonyms like
that so based on that intuition we
developed llm query highlight expansions
and going forward I'll just call these
llm expansions so these essentially
expand the query into various Rel Rel
ated phrases or key Concepts so we
started out with a pretty simple set of
expansions right so you can see um
couple of years ago what we had uh
fairly simple and then over months or
years we've iterated to sort of arrive
at the expansion type that we have today
which is the one towards the bottom over
here and over iterations one thing that
was really important to us was
reusability or modularity so we really
focused on being on developing
expansions that could be uh pluggable
into various different use cases so one
thing that helps a lot with that is this
Steed system that we have here so uh all
of the the suggested key Concepts or
relevant phrases are sort of ordered in
tiers of relevance so the first tier is
very relevant the second tier less
relevant and so on and this helps a lot
with modularity we can plug it into
different use cases in one use case we
might choose to use only uh the first
year of relevance in another we might
choose to use many and so on um and yeah
if you want to know a bit more about uh
llm expansions and these it iterations
they were actually discussed in a hyack
us talk earlier this year and feel free
to scan the QR code uh if you're
interested I'll just wait on this for a
couple of
seconds cool um okay so now that we've
seen what these qu llm expansions look
like I'll talk a bit more about how we
leverage them for
annotations so the first annotation that
we we'll talk about is one that we've
already had a quick glimpse into which
is review highlights so this is a very
high level overview of what the review
highlights infrastructure looked like
before we uh started tweaking it so when
Once uh a business is chosen to be shown
on the sub the business is sent into the
annotator service to fetch
annotations and if you remember this is
the service responsible for pulling in
all of that data right to create the
annotations so as part of that one of
the annotations that creates is review
highlights and it does this by
constructing a review highlights query
in which it tries to match against the
user search query so it uh creates this
review highlights query sends it to the
review search engine which is uh built
on top of Lucine and the best high best
matching highlight if it exists is found
and returned to the annotator service
where as long as it passes some quality
checks it can then be returned to show
on the
Ser
so as we were looking at this
architecture and evaluating how to
incorporate llm llm expansions into it
we noticed that there were also a few
other shortcomings that our old system
had so we knew that we wanted to retain
as much as the retrieval functionality
as we could and we realized that by
incorporating ating expansions and also
making some small tweaks we could uh use
the backbone of our table system improve
it and arrive at something much more
powerful so I'm going to talk about
those improvements
now so the first one is query
understanding which is mainly where the
llm expansions come into the
picture so as uh as I showed in the
architecture diagram previously we were
only matching on the user search query
text initially while fetching highlights
so after making this uh Improvement of
incorporating llm expansions instead of
matching just on the user search query
we try to match on any of the expanded
phrases for that search query so in the
example of healthy food if a user had
searched for healthy food previously we
would have only fetched highlights that
matched healthy food now we fetch
highlights that match any of the 12
phrases listed over here on average uh
we have eight phrases per search
query so this has a few uh interesting
benefits so the first benefit is that we
see a lot more uh diversity of
highlights on the soap so it just looks
a bit more interesting right like you
can see from all of these examples if
you saw them on a Serb the Serb just
looks a little more interesting than if
you had highlights where healthy food
was highlighted every single time the
other benefit is coverage so you uh you
might have some businesses that are
shown on a soap for healthy food but
they don't have any queries sorry they
don't have any reviews that actually
mention healthy food and so previously
we wouldn't have been able to show a
review highlight on these businesses but
now that we match on all of these new
phrases it's highly likely that one of
those businesses has a mention for
nutritious or organic or something so in
this way we can show review highlights
on more businesses by integrating llm
expansions and then finally we also see
improvements in quality so for example
if you think back to the affordable hair
salons example um previously we would
have tried to match on a affordable hair
salons or n gs of it and so we might
have occasionally matched on hair
salons whereas the optimal thing to do
is actually to match on affordable or
synonyms of affordable which we would do
now so there are many cases like this
where the search query itself is not is
not necessarily the exact best thing to
match on which llm expansions helps with
and also just to add we we have llm
expansions stored for a huge set of
queries that covers most of yel traffic
but for unseen queries that we don't
have expansions for we have a smart
heuristic that uh that sort of
understands what categories of
businesses the user is looking for and
uses the expansions of those categories
to uh fetch highlights and it works very
well so a benefit of using switching
from search query text to llm expansions
is that it's very easy to slot this into
our existing architecture without really
needing an overhaul you can see that
basically it just replaces the query
building phase with uh the llm
expansions so next we'll talk about
another Improv ment that we made in our
retrieval system so our previous system
was a bit inflexible in that it would
only return one top highlights match
from the review search engine we updated
this logic to start returning five
matches instead to give us additional
control over the type of highlight that
we show and we wanted this additional
control because the retrieval and
ranking that's done on the review search
engine does doesn't really capture all
of the information or intuition that we
would want it
to so intuitively we care about uh much
more than just the highlighted phrase we
care about the recency of the review
from which we're pulling the Highlight
we care about how grammatically correct
the sentence or the review highlighters
we also care about representing the
business ACC accurately so for example
for a five-star business we wouldn't
want to fetch a really low rated review
uh for the review highlight and vice
versa so you can see some I'm I'm not
sure if the coloring is super visible
but like this is red green green red um
but basically you can see in some of
these examples that even though each of
these highlights uh has a match for the
same phrase go and corn dog in the first
pair we would prefer the more recent one
over the older one because it's just a
much stronger signal of relevance proof
to the user and then in the second one
based on sort of the grammatical
structure of the sentence we would
prefer the top one over the second one
just because it's a much more coherent
uh
thought so to incorporate this intuition
we allow the review search engine to
return top five matches to us these top
five matches are based on the uh
closeness the text match and then we
rank them basically based on additional
features and these additional features
are just captured through very simple
numerical functions and we learned uh
simple ways to uh to calculate the final
score again similar to llm expansions
you can see how the slots pretty easily
into our existing architecture all we
had to do was start returning top five
matches from the review search engine
which is a capability available to us
and then we just had to create a new
small ranking module which was fairly
simple and then another quick uh benefit
of uh returning five candidates is that
we now have the ability to filter
inappropriate content without
hurting the coverage of our review
highlights so this doesn't happen
frequently but it is of course possible
that the review search engine will find
a strong match for the text that we're
looking for but the uh the review
highlight might be inappropriate to show
on the soap for various reasons that
there could be some inappropriate
language in it it could be very weirdly
formatted like you know inconsistent
capitalization
or there could be like addresses or
phone numbers in it so we wouldn't want
to show any of these things on the so
and we're able to just filter it out and
show the next best
candidate and then the final set of
improvements I want to talk about is
related to handling Text data so we
noticed some areas of improvement that
fall under this text Data umbrella one
of the pretty simple improvements was
that the highlights previously that we
had were clipped at word boundaries and
so they wouldn't necessarily always make
sense as a coherent thought so we made a
pretty simple switch the review search
engine allows us to clip at sentence
boundaries instead so we just made that
switch to have more coherent highlights
but another thing that we looked into
was handling bad stemming so just like
quick background I'm sure most folks are
probably aware but stemming is the
process of reducing a word to its root
or its stem in this case taking an
example of active all of the words
active activity activities actively they
would all stem to the
same so you can imagine that if you were
running a search for
activities you wouldn't want to see
highlights for the word active or
actively because they mean something
pretty different in this context but the
review search engine doesn't really
understand that context right so it uh
it can tend to return some uh matches
that don't really make sense all the
time and so we actually ended up
deciding to maintain a hardcoded list of
incorrect stemming and we use that for
filtering so again because we have five
candidates return to us it's pretty easy
for us to filter out a candidate if it
has bad stemming and we still have have
uh matched to fall back
on so the result of all of the
improvements that I've mentioned is a
smarter retrieval flow that leverages
llm expansions smart ranking or ranking
and uh also leverages existing retrieval
capabilities all in order to provide
much smarter and higher quality
highlights than it was possible to
return before and with higher coverage
than
before and yeah just kind of a
combination of all of the Improvement
architecture diagrams that IID mentioned
this is what the final infrastructure
looks like so you can see it's super
close to what we had before just with a
few improvements and tweaks in some
places and here is a quick example of
the old highlights compared to the new
highlights I'm not sure sure how visible
it is everywhere but uh you can see that
in the old system the sentences were
kind of incomplete they weren't
necessarily full thoughts and even
though you could tell that the business
did of the dish you're looking for it
wasn't too clear what the sentiment was
in the reviews that we pulled the
highlights from on the other hand in the
new system you can see that each thought
is a lot more complete and the sentiment
is much more clear so this just provides
a much stronger relevance proof and like
trust I
guess cool so we've seen the power of
small tweaks and llm expansions in an
existing
annotation and next I want to talk about
the power of using llm expansions to
build a new
annotation so uh The Guiding question
for building this next annotation was
how can we provide relevance proof for
low content or unreviewed businesses
because the review highlights that we
were talking about were very focused on
businesses that have a lot of uh you
know Yelp user generated content right
in the form of
reviews so some businesses provide Yelp
with their website URLs and their
website data which allows us to make use
of their website text and this can be
especially powerful for businesses that
don't have a lot of content on Yelp yet
so you can imagine for this fake website
that I made up if someone had searched
for like butter chicken or Kai chicken I
could very easily find a way to surface
some data from their Business website to
prove to the user that this business is
indeed relevant for their search query
so we have access to all of this website
data but it's just too much data for us
to store on our uh on our search index
or you know it's it's too much for us to
store for retrieval basically so just
looking at this again like fake example
of a paragraph on the side you can tell
that because of the presence of like
HTML tags and a lot of stop words and
maybe some words that just aren't us
useful for annotations or retrieval
there's a lot of unnecessary text
basically that isn't useful for us on
Yelp and isn't useful for us to show to
users so that brings us to the question
of information synthesis which is how do
how best to store this data such that it
retains its meaning uh and still is high
quality enough for us to use
so the answer again is llm
expansions so what we do is we create a
resource of phrases that we care about
or phrases that we want to match on and
this resource is basically um a bunch of
top historical search queries let's say
from the last few years and for each of
those search queries we uh we also pull
in all of the LLS expansions for those
queries so that whole set of phrases is
going to be our phrase data set and
that's the full set of phrases that we
want to match on so what we do is we can
safely look for these phrases in the
business's websites and then for each
business we end up storing a map of
phrases to the number of times that
they're mentioned on the Business
website so any of the other text from
the website is not something we care
about so now that we have all of that
data uh stored we can then expose it in
order to build annotations so the per
the per business phrase count data set
is stored on some in in some data
storage that's exposed through a Content
endpoint and then again we have the
annotator service
which is able to call the content
endpoint to fetch these phrases so the
structure is very very similar to what
we saw for review highlights essentially
a business query is sent to the
annotator service the annotator service
looks up the phrases the llm expansions
for the search query and then it fetches
the mentions for each of those phrases
for this particular business and
constructs an annotation using the most
relevant phrase that's mentioned on the
business's
website so finally here are some
examples of what these annotations look
like um yeah not again sorry not sure if
every single thing is visible at the
back but you can see that because we've
used llm expansions to uh to generate
the or to mine the data as well as to
fetch The annotation
in some cases The annotation shown
matches the search query text exactly
such as for nutrition plan but in some
other cases you can see that The
annotation is either like a synonym of
the search query text or a phrase that's
kind of related to the search query text
so here again we can see the power of
those llm expansions coming through to
provide more coverage basically uh in
these annotations and you can also see
that these annotations are showing up on
businesses that are pretty low content
so they have you know five reviews or
less so again we're providing some sort
of strong relevance proof for businesses
that we don't have too much data
about cool so now that we've spoken
about uh some of the uses of llms in our
current annotations I just want to think
talk a bit about how we're thinking
about this problem going forward and the
kinds of iterations and improvements
that we want to
make so we're super interested in the
reusability of existing signals uh in a
similar way to how we've captured
information from the business's websites
we've also actually used the exact same
approach to capture information from the
business's menus reviews photo captions
and so on so all of this was Yelp
content
but we've sort of summarized it in this
way and then we plan to use these
signals to generate very similar
annotations to website mentions such as
on the menu or X number of reviews
mention a certain
phrase and then also just want to call
out that our website mention signal is
also reusable for non annotations use
cases such as retrieval
and then we were also thinking about how
to actually use llms directly in
highlight selection so you know in in
all of the stuff that I spoke about
previously we're kind of using llms
indirectly right in using llm expansions
but then using more traditional
retrieval methods so we're thinking
about how we can use llms directly and
you know you can imagine a very simple
case of
uh an llm takes a business and the
search query and all of the recent
reviews of the business and decides
which span of text from those recent
reviews should be shown to the user and
which part of it should be bolded right
so it's kind of like choosing the review
highlight completely for the business
and something like this could be very
useful for more generic searches like
restaurants or food where
the relevance of the businesses is quite
obvious just at a glance and so the
kinds of things that we want might want
to highlight in review highlights is um
something interesting like the place was
memorable right or something that's not
directly a synonym of the search query
basically and then finally llms could
also
select uh could also generate an
annotation directly for the business
instead of sort of selecting from the
selecting from the existing business
data it could be the one to generate The
annotation so given the context of a
search query as well as all of the
search results on the page an llm could
decide what makes each business on the
page relevant and appealing and then
generate an annotation to show so
this could look something like this
where an llm decides that the F for the
first result would makes it unique and
different from the other results is that
their specialty is Korean corn dogs
whereas for the second business what
sets it apart from the other businesses
on the page is that they have sort of
beginner friendly half and half options
so this is just an example but it could
also be useful for those generic type of
queries like restaurants and food again
cool so the last thing that I want to
talk about is another way that we've
leveraged the annotator
service so everyone's probably very
familiar with the word the you know
acronym rag but yeah just uh to
reiterate rag stands for retrieval
augmented generation and it's the
approach of optimizing the output of an
llm by providing ing it with some
external data source or some knowledge
base and Yelp has a lot of data and you
can imagine that for Yelp specific use
cases it might be helpful to have Yelp
specific information provided to an llm
right so something that you might have
also noticed by now is that the
annotator service essentially features
as a fact finding service for a business
right so given a business your
essentially fetching all of this
information about it and then returning
just the top
information so there were various teams
that y that started to notice this and
approached us asking whether we would
expose the annotator service for Rag and
we ended up creating a rag specific
endpoint to satisfy that demand so the
way that it works is the new endpoint
takes a business ID or set of business
IDs and optionally takes a search query
term and then it returns a bunch of
information relevant to that business so
recent reviews of the business uh
properties of the business features of
the business um phae phase mention
Counts from like websites photo captions
and so on and then it also if a search
query text had been pass in then it also
returns uh phrase review highlights
relevant to that search query text and
then the way that this might be used for
a Yelp product there could be a Q&A
product on the bu at the business level
for example so a user might be able to
ask the Q&A product a question about a
business such as does McDonald's in
Berlin have vegan options or something
right so then the Q&A product extracts
something from that query which is like
McDonald's Bur and the word vegan right
and it sends it over to the annotator
service the annotator service pulls a
lot of information about McDonald's Bull
in and it also looks up in the reviews
for uh review highlights that match the
word vegan and then it consolidates all
of this information sends it back to the
Q&A product and then the Q&A product
uses all of this information adds it to
the llm prompt and then gets an answer
to send back to the user so currently
the annotator service for rag is only
used internally but hopefully there
might be some external use cases
soon cool so that was everything I
wanted to talk about just some quick
takeaways to sort of uh unify you know
everything that I've spoken about I
think one of the big things that we care
about and were really interested in
while designing all of these things is
reusability and repurposing we were
really interested in designing llm
signals that could be reused wherever
possible so you've seen that the llm
expansions that I spoke about were um
reused in review highlights but also in
website mentions for both uh
synthesizing the data and also for
generating the annotations and then you
know even when a comes to the annotator
service we use it for you know its
traditional uh purpose for annotating
businesses on the serp but we also
reused it for rag so we're really
interested in yeah using things for
various
purposes also
um we're always uh careful to find the
right balance between sort of llm
strategies and you know more Legacy
strategies I guess so
in the review highlights example you
could see that we used llm expansions in
some places but in other places we kind
of took a step back and just used manual
tweaks or small changes and got a lot of
value out of it right and then finally
yeah just uh wanted to stress that we're
always interested in continuous
iteration and so we yeah have various
other plans in mind for review
highlights and annotations in general
and we want to continue seeing how we
can use llms and other strategies in
them and yeah that's all I had thank you
so much thank you very
much thank
you great so we have time for a few
questions and I want to start off with
uh questions from the online audience uh
the first couple of questions is around
uh the llm expansion
itself um Jack V ask
um how did you balance the llm expansion
with any drop in Precision for example
Falafel might be fresh but not
necessarily
healthy um and maybe related to this
question from udal uh also how do you
assess the quality of LM expansions what
are the metrics to track yeah so um in
in terms of precision um s can you
repeat the Precision question so how do
you balance the LM expansions with any
drop in prisions so recall vers prision
more or less in LM expansions and then
what are the metrics to to track yeah I
mean I I think like one major thing is
we went through a lot of iterations of
our Alam expansions so uh I'm not
claiming that we like got it right the
first time right so we had a lot we I
think we ran like four or five
experiments on different sets of llm
expansions where we recognized that each
uh stage had certain shortcomings like
in some stages we were expanding too
much right so then running into the
issue of having too many phrases and
then recalling lower quality uh
highlights some of the times so we were
pretty careful to do a lot of manual
evaluation like we have internal tools
that allow us to simulate a lot of
searches and see what the review
highlights see what the annotations
would look like so there was a lot of
manual evaluation a lot of involvement
from product in sort of helping us
evaluate those things so that's uh
primarily how we assessed uh things like
quality because yeah I mean the scale of
this product is pretty huge it's pretty
hard for us to um yeah kind of do
quality evaluations at a large enough
scale to cover every single possible
search query so it's more of a manual
effort also looking at search metrics
various search metrics and trying to
decipher the way that why they're moving
the way they're moving um but yeah just
went through a lot of iterations okay
thanks any questions from the floor uh
there yeah so thanks for the talk uh I
have one question on the uh using llms
for term expansion so in your iteration
of experiments like on which model which
one to use for term expansion so did you
consider using um machine learning
models which are which are like which
are trained to do this expansion for
example we have lexical SP expansion
models like splade or of like open
search has few things did you consider
any of these options like in your
experimentations like of doing the term
expansion other than
llms um yeah I think that's a really
good question I can get back to you on
an answer so I mean yeah I I guess like
what I didn't mention is uh everything
involved in this is obviously the result
of a huge team's work not just mine and
so there was a different engineer who
worked on the actual llm expansions so
I'm happy to check on that and get back
to you there was another hand up here
somewhere
thanks for the talk um quick question
are these expansions personalized so can
you have a different highlights for
different users or are they tied to the
query and the business itself like do
you have different highlights or not
yeah the highlights right now are not
personalized so the llm expansions are
the same across uh all users uh
actually we well I mean a lot of yel
users aren't always logged in um a lot
of our sessions come
from via like Google right so a lot of
times yeah uh we don't have enough user
information to make a judgment call we
of course do have a lot of logged in
users a lot of um opportunities for
personalization but for the first few
stages it didn't seem worth the
investment of
yeah okay thank you I'm afraid we had
time but I think you'll be you you be
around and uh be open for questions and
also thanks to the online audience for
your questions uh just a quick break uh
don't run away so we just changed the
setup here another round of applause
sorry